rarehistoricalphotos.com 2019-12-11

# Privacy Policy - Rare Historical Photos

This Privacy Policy governs the manner in which RareHistoricalPhotos.com collects, uses, maintains and discloses information collected from users (“user”) of the RareHistoricalPhotos.com website (“site”). This privacy policy applies to the site and all products and services offered by RareHistoricalPhotos.com.  
**  
Personal identification information**  
We may collect personal identification information from users in a variety of ways, including, but not limited to, when users visit our site, subscribe to the newsletter, and in connection with other activities, services, features or resources we make available on our site. Users may be asked for, as appropriate, name, email address. Users may, however, visit our site anonymously. We will collect personal identification information from users only if they voluntarily submit such information to us. Users can always refuse to supply personally identification information, except that it may prevent them from engaging in certain site related activities.  
**  
Non-personal identification information**  
We may collect non-personal identification information about users whenever they interact with our site. Non-personal identification information may include the browser name, the type of computer and technical information about users means of connection to our site, such as the operating system and the Internet service providers utilized and other similar information.

 **Web browser cookies**  
Our site may use “cookies” to enhance user experience. User’s web browser places cookies on their hard drive for record-keeping purposes and sometimes to track information about them. Overall, cookies help us provide you with a better website, by enabling us to monitor which pages you find useful and which you do not. A cookie in no way gives us access to your computer or any information about you, other than the data you choose to share with us. User may choose to set their web browser to refuse cookies, or to alert you when cookies are being sent. If they do so, note that some parts of the site may not function properly.

 **How we use collected information**  
RareHistoricalPhotos.com may collect and use users personal information for the following purposes:

  * To improve customer service (information you provide helps us respond to your customer service requests and support needs more efficiently).
  * To improve our Site (we may use feedback you provide to improve our products and services).

 **Links to other websites**  
Our website may contain links to other websites of interest. However, once you have used these links to leave our site, you should note that we do not have any control over that other website. Therefore, we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide whilst visiting such sites and such sites are not governed by this privacy statement. You should exercise caution and look at the privacy statement applicable to the website in question.

 **Security**  
We adopt appropriate data collection, storage and processing practices and security measures to protect against unauthorized access, alteration, disclosure or destruction of your personal information, username, password, transaction information and data stored on our Site. Sensitive and private data exchange between the Site and its Users happens over a SSL secured communication channel and is encrypted and protected with digital signatures.

 **Sharing your personal information**  
We do not sell, trade, or rent users personal identification information to others. We may share generic aggregated demographic information not linked to any personal identification information regarding visitors and users with our business partners, trusted affiliates and advertisers for the purposes outlined above.

 **Changes to this privacy policy and your acceptance of these terms**  
RareHistoricalPhotos.com has the discretion to update this privacy policy at any time. When we do, we will post a notification on the main page of our Site. We encourage Users to frequently check this page for any changes to stay informed about how we are helping to protect the personal information we collect. You acknowledge and agree that it is your responsibility to review this privacy policy periodically and become aware of modifications. By using this Site, you signify your acceptance of this policy.

 **Contacting us**  
If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this site, please [contact us here](https://rarehistoricalphotos.com/contact/).

 _This document was last updated on August 19, 2014._
